Raymond, Eleanor. The Eleanor Raymond Collection: An Inventory.
Eleanor Raymond Collection.
- Series C / Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice, / Date(s): 1946; C000
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo Mussell Point House, / Date(s): --; : C002
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white photograph of the cottage from the rocks; 14" x 20", mounted on gatorboard.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo Cleaves House, / Date(s): --; : C003
    Content: Flat file contains 1 colored photograph of plans and elevation drawing; 13" x 17", unmounted and sepia toned.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo 112 Charles Street, Boston, / Date(s): --; : C004
    Content: Box #1 contains 5 glass lantern slides of garden of Raymond House, 112 Charles Street, Boston, MA.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo High Spruces, Haddam, / Date(s): --; : C005
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white photograph of garden from second story window; 17-1/2" x 22", unmounted.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo 112 Charles Street, Boston, / Date(s): --; : C006
    Content: Flat file contains 6 black and white photographs: 2 garden photos, 6" x 9", mounted, by Sayre; 1 out back window, 16" x 19", mounted; 3 garden photos 7-1/2" x 9-1/2", unmounted by Church (?).
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo Rachel C. Raymond House, / Date(s): --; : C007
    Content: Flat file contains 9 black and white photographs: 3 mounted with labels for Boston Society of Architects 1938 Exhibit, 16" x 20"; 6 unmounted 16-1/2" x 24", 8-1/2" x 11", 16" x 20", 16-1/2" x 24", 6" x 9-1/2".
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: TZE House, / Date(s): --; : C008
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white exterior photograph by Doris Cole; 8" x 10", unmounted. Also contains photographic print of pencil drawing showing plans, sections and elevations; 17" x 22", unmounted.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo Safford House, / Date(s): --; : C009
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white photograph; 14" x 21", unmounted.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo Remodelled House for Mary Byers Smith, / Date(s): --; : C010
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white photograph; 1927; 7-1/2" x 9-1/2", mounted with label (damaged mounting).
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photographs, / Date(s): --; : C011
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white photograph of rendering by Kay Petersen (last name illegible); 7-1/2" x 9-1/2", mounted, by Church, of building, unidentified.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Photo Garden of Mrs. John Potter, / Date(s): --; : C012
    Content: Flat file contains 3 black and white garden photographs by Paul J. Weber, Architectural Photographer, Boston, MA, 8" x 10"; 1 photostat of garden rendering, 6-1/2" x 8-1/2"; 1 paper print of garden photo, 6-1/2" x 9".
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Rendering Modern House, / Date(s): --; : C013
    Content: Flat file contains 1 unidentified rendering of single-story modern house with trellis and glass porch; labelled "Eleanor Raymond Architect" and "Brodie (del)"; small plan in lower corner; 13-3/4" x 8", pencil on board.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Eleanor Raymond's Scrapbook, / Date(s): 1981; : C014
    Note: Eleanor Raymond's scrapbook at the time of ICA Exhibit and Doris Cole Exhibit. Contains: reviews, articles, guest lists, list of projects photos of ICA Exhibit.
    Content: Box #1 contains this scrapbook.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Negatives Rachel Raymond House, / Date(s): 1981; : C015
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white negative; 8" x 11" in envelope.
  - Photos, Other Graphic Material and Memorabilia / Professional Practice: Negatives Cleaves House Drawing, / Date(s): 1981; : C016
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white negative of Cleaves House drawing; 8" x 10" in envelope.
- Series D / Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life, / Date(s): 1981; D000
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Eleanor Raymond's Diary, / Date(s): 1981; : D001
    Note: Eleanor Raymond's personal diary.
    Content: Box #1 contains this diary.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Eleanor Raymond's Diary, / Date(s): 1973; : D002
    Note: Eleanor Raymond's personal diary for the year 1973.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Ethel Power's Gloucester Diary, / Date(s): 1944-1951; : D003
    Note: Ethel Power's diary of summers spent in the cottage she shared with Eleanor Raymond at Mussel Point, Gloucester, MA between the years 1951 and 1967.
    Content: Box #2 contains this typed, unbound paper diary.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Ethel Power's Gloucester Diary, / Date(s): 1951-1967; : D004
    Content: Box #2 contains this diary.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Ethel Power's Mexico Diary, / Date(s): 1965-1968; : D005
    Note: Ethel Power's diary of trip with Eleanor Raymond to Mexico. Diary dated 1965-1968. This is one of three.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Eleanor Raymond's Student Album, / Date(s): 1909; : D006
    Note: Eleanor Raymond's photograph album of student life at Wellesley College, Wellesley, MA, 1909.
    Content: Box #2 contains this photograph album.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Rachel Raymond's Album, / Date(s): 1960's; : D007
    Note: Album of photographs taken by Rachel Raymond at an unidentified barn location.
    Content: Box #1 contains this album.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Rachel Raymond's Panoramics Album, / Date(s): 1963; : D008
    Note: Group of panoramic photographs taken by Rachel Raymond, Christmas, 1963, at an unidentified barn location.
    Content: Box #1 contains this group of photographs.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Photo Charles Goldman, / Date(s): --; : D009
    Content: Box #1 contains 1 black and white photograph of Raymond friend and attorney Goldman (not labeled) sent to Sandra Raymond (Eleanor's niece) from Widett, Slater & Goldman; 4" x 6", unmounted, in envelope.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Ethel Power's Photographs, / Date(s): --; : D010
    Note: Photograph titles: "Lake Palsumaro"; "Winter Sun"; "Spring Water"; "Tarlascan Indians."
    Content: Flat file contains 4 black and white photographs signed by Ethel Power.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Photograph Eleanor Raymond, / Date(s): --; : D011
    Note: Flat file contains black and white portrait photograph of Eleanor Raymond (photographer's name illegible); 1937; 6-1/2" x 10-3/4", unmounted.
  - Manuscript and Graphic Material / Personal Life: Negatives Eleanor Raymond Portrait, / Date(s): --; : D012
    Content: Flat file contains 1 black and white negative of portrait of Eleanor Raymond as a young lady; 8" x 10" in envelope.
- Series E / Eleanor Raymond Addendum, E000
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E001; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior photographs of Hammond Compound, Gloucester, MA. Built 1941. This envelope "House #1" (Stone Residence).
    Note: See also A419.
    Provenance: Photographs in this series are a gift of Nancy Beth Gruskin, 1990's.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E002; / Quantity: 26 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior and exterior photographs of Gordon Parker House. Built 1941.
    Note: See also A416.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E003; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior and exterior photographs of Theodore Miller House. Built 1936.
    Note: See also A365.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E004; / Quantity: 4 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior photographs of Irvine House Addition. Built 1963-64.
    Note: See also A6312.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E005; / Quantity: 6 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior photographs of Hammond Compound, Gloucester, MA. Built 1941. This envelope "House #2" (King Residence).
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E006; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Exterior photographs of Hammond Compound, Gloucester, MA. Built 1941.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E007; / Quantity: 11 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior and exterior photographs of Rachel Raymond House. Built 1931.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E008; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior and exterior photographs of Irvine House, Belmont, MA.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E009; / Quantity: 9 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior and exterior photographs of Frost House, Cambridge, MA.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Envelope: E010; / Quantity: 13 / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: b&w / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Interior and exterior photographs of Nichols Factory, Waltham, MA.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E011; / Quantity: 17 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of 112 Charles Street; Frost House and bulk of Raymond's Summer House at Mussel Point.
    Provenance: Slides in this series are a gift of Nancy Beth Gruskin, 1990's.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E012; / Quantity: 15 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Raymond's Summer House at Mussel Point.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E013; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Frost House and additional house.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E014; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Amelia Peabody Studio and Theodore Miller House (Belmont, MA, 1936).
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E015; / Quantity: 19 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of High Spruces House in Connecticut. Parker House in Winchester, and Sun House in Dover, Massachusetts.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E016; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Hammond Compound.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E017; / Quantity: 20 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of interiors (Hammond Compound?)
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E018; / Quantity: 16 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Nichols Factory and Irvine House.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E019; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Frost House in Cambridge and of Farm Group in Dover, MA.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), Folder: E020; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: 2" x 2" / Medium: color / Support: acetate
    Note: Folder contains sheet with slides of Gordon Parker House in Winchester, MA.
  - Eleanor Raymond Addendum: Photographs and Slides (from Nancy Gruskin), : E021; / Quantity: 2 / Medium: film
    Note: File contains 2 rolls of undeveloped film.
Personal Names Index
Adams, Mrs. Franklin P. (client) / Blueprints A4704
Adams, Mrs. Franklin P. (client) / Correspondence A6107
Alden (client) / Correspondence A6701
Alexander (client) / Invoices A6503
Anderson (client) / Design development drawings A4605
Anderson (client) / Project files A458
Atkins, Dr. / Diazo process prints A6306
Atkins (client) / Correspondence A6202
Atkinson (client) / Measured drawings A5013
Babcock (client) / Correspondence A6103
Ballantine, Mrs. Edward (client) / Construction drawings A3715
Ballantine, Mrs. Edward (client) / Project files A407, A4311
Barnes, Frank E. (client) / Blueline prints A4517
Barnes, Frank E. (client) / Construction drawings A2912
Barnes, Frank E. (client) / Project files A442
Barr (client) / Correspondence A5912
Bartel, William P. (client) / Construction drawings A377
Bass, Mrs. Robert P. (client) / Blueprints A4719
Bass-Perkins (client) / Project files A4813
Baxter-Ward (client) / Correspondence A7005
Baxter-Ward (client) / Invoices A7007
Beebe (client) / Design development drawings A4717
Besse, Arthur (client) / Construction drawings A398
Blewer, John M. (client) / Construction drawings A6401
Blewer, Mr. & Mrs. Francis L. (client) / Construction drawings A6408
Blewer, Mr. & Mrs. Francis L. (client) / Correspondence A5805, A6704
Blewer, Mr. & Mrs. Francis L. (client) / Design development drawings A7102
Blewer, Mr. & Mrs. Francis L. (client) / Diazo process prints A4903
Blewer (client) / Cuts A7202
Blick (client) / Construction drawings A4629
Border, H. (client) / Construction drawings A4814
Bowditch, Mr. & Mrs. Richard L. (client) / Correspondence A5702
Bowditch, Mr. & Mrs. Richard L. (client) / Design development drawings A5301
Bowditch, Mr. & Mrs. Richard L. (client) / Project files A6402
Bowditch (client) / Correspondence A6001, A6111
Bowditch (client) / Diazo process prints A6301
Bowman (client) / Diazo process prints A5503
Boynton, Alvah (client) / Correspondence A5804
Bradley, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (client) / Blueprints A4918
Bradley, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (client) / Correspondence A6806
Bradley, Mr. & Mrs. Ralph (client) / Measured drawings A5416
Brennan (client) / Project files A4611
Brodie (delineator) / Construction drawings A416
Brodie (delineator) / Renderings C013
Brookings (client) / Building codes A6606
Brookings (client) / Construction drawings A7003
Brookings (client) / Project files A7402
Brown, Mr. & Mrs. Samuel C. (client) / Details A7011
Brown, Mr. & Mrs. Samuel C. (client) / Diazo process prints A7209
Bucknell (client) / Construction drawings A6406
Burrill (client) / Construction drawings A4712
Burroughs (client) / Correspondence A6801
Burton (client) / Construction drawings A5601
Buswell (client) / Project files A444
Cabot, George (client) / Blueprints A4919
Cabot, George (client) / Design development drawings A5109
Cabot (client) / Blueprints A6904
Callahan (client) / Negatives A7104
Chase, John P. (client) / Correspondence A6808
Chase, Mrs. Carroll (client) / Correspondence A6307
Chase (client) / Correspondence A5610
Churchill, Mrs. Lawrence (client) / Clippings A6104
Churchill, Mrs. Lawrence (client) / Correspondence A5806
Churchill, Mrs. Lawrence (owner) / Clippings A6106
Cleaves (client) / Article B008
Cleaves (client) / Photographs C003
Close (client) / Design development drawings A4817
Cole, Doris (architect) / Manuscripts B017
Cole, Doris (architect) / Personal papers B018
Cole, Doris (author) / Manuscripts B017
Cole, Doris (author) / Personal papers B018
Cole, Doris (friend) / Manuscripts B017
Conant, Mrs. Nelson (client) / Correspondence A5712
Conant, Mrs. Nelson (client) / Project files A4907
Coon, Carleton (client) / Correspondence A5714
Cram (client) / Project files A4720
Crane (client) / Correspondence A6105
Crosby, William A. (client) / Blueprints A456
Cushman, Charlotte (previous owner) / Correspondence A5905
Cushman (client) / Correspondence A5903
Damon (client) / Clippings A6106
Danforth (client) / Contracts A5704
Danforth (client) / Correspondence A6409
Dexter (client) / Contracts A5918
Dexter (client) / Correspondence A5921
Dickerson, Ellen (client) / Construction drawings A4715
Dickerson (client) / Blueprints A7008
Dodge (original architect) / Blueprints A4919
Donovan (client) / Blueprints A5014
Doriot (client) / Notes A5019
Doriot (client) / Project files A6006
Douglas (client) / Project files A4530
Dumaine (client) / Correspondence A6512
Dunsford (client) / Project files A4623
Eaton, W.M. (client) / Correspondence A6513
Eliot (client) / Construction drawings A6410
Elliott, Herford N. (client) / Construction drawings A3517
Ellis, Mrs. Dorothy R. (client) / Articles B003
Ellis (client) / Articles B003
Ellis (client) / Bids A6101
Ellis (client) / Brochures A7303
Ellis (client) / Correspondence A6204
Ellis (client) / Project files A4710
Fall (client) / Project files A5102
Farnsworth, Marion B. (client) / Articles B001
Farnsworth, Marion B. (client) / Blueprints A386, A4017, A447
Farnsworth, Marion B. (client) / Construction drawings A3516, A353, A389, A395
Farnsworth, Marion B. (client) / Correspondence A5703, A5804
Farnsworth, Marion B. (client) / Measured drawings A5412
Farnsworth, Marion B. (client) / Project files A372, A378, A384, A387, A417
Fitzgibbon (friend) / Correspondence A6702
Fitzgibon (client) / Blueprints A4602
Forbes (client) / Clippings A6005
Frost, Horace W. (client) / Measured drawings A4528
Frost, Horace W. (client) / Outline specifications A3518
Fuller (client) / Correspondence A5811
Gardiner, Tudor / Correspondence A5608
Gilfillan, Mrs. Edward (client) / Building programs A7403
Goldman, Charles (friend) / Photographs D009
Goldman, Charles (lawyer) / Photographs D009
Goldthwaite, Dr. (client) / Photographs A275
Greene (client) / Correspondence A5612
Greene (client) / Project files A5304, A5405
Gring, Mrs. Paul / Appeals A6502
Grote / Correspondence A7006
Gruskin, Nancy Beth (photographer) / Film, roll E021
Gruskin, Nancy Beth (photographer) / Photographs E001, E002, E003, E004, E005, E006, E007, E008, E009, E010
Gruskin, Nancy Beth (photographer) / Slides E012, E013, E014, E015, E016, E017, E018, E019, E020
Hagar, Donald / Diazo process prints A5216
Hammond, Natalie (client) / Construction drawings A419
Harkness, Sarah (Pillsbury), (assistant architect) / Construction drawings A3717
Harkness, Sarah (Pillsbury), (client) / Construction drawings A3717
Harrison, Dorothea K. (landscape architect) / Construction drawings A4511
Harrison, Dorothea K. (landscape architect) / Correspondence A5805
Harrison, Hartman K. (client) / Project files A5519
Harrold (client) / Construction drawings A7207
Hart (client) / Correspondence A6603
Haskell, Mrs. Richard (client) / Correspondence A6212
Hazard, Vincent (client) / Project files A5520
Henry (client) / Correspondence A5908
Hight (client) / Project files A4627
Hill, John (client) / Correspondence A5707
Horowitz (client) / Correspondence A6214
Howard (client) / Correspondence A5803
Hubbard, Mr. & Mrs. Charles (client) / Contracts A6703
Hubbard (client) / Correspondence A5922
Hunt, Bishop (client) / Correspondence A6405, A6711
Hunt, Mrs. Albert (client) / Blueprints A386
Hunt, Mrs. Albert (client) / Design development drawings A7401
Hutchison (client) / Construction drawings A6601
Ingelfinger (client) / Blueprints A5710
Irvine (client) / Bids A6312
Jackson, Mr. William K. (client) / Articles B009
Jackson (client) / Design development drawings A5403
Jackson (client) / Project files A446
Jacobson (client) / Clippings A5802
Jacobson (client) / Correspondence A5905
Jenny (client) / Project files A5902
Johannet, Dr. Pierre (client) / Landscape plans A5402
Johnson (client) / Construction drawings A5116, A5812
Jordan (client) / Correspondence A6302, A6812
Katzeff (client) / Project files A4620
Ketchum (client) / Correspondence A6304
Kinkade (client) / Invoices A7307
Kirkwood, Grace (landscape architect) / Construction drawings A5616
Kirkwood-Dupee, Mr. & Mrs. Donald C. / Correspondence A5910
Kirkwood-Milliken (client) / Correspondence A5807
Leach (owner) / Notes A7301
Legg, Mrs. John C. III (client) / Photographs A5518
Lennihan, Richard H. (client) / Articles B010
Long, Harriet P. (landscape architect) / Bids A5916
MacInnis (client) / Measured drawings A4512
MacLeish, Mrs. (client) / Project files A4920
MacMillan, Mrs. (landscape draftsman?) / Design development drawings A5107
Mallery (client) / Correspondence A6706
Manville (client) / Project files A5605
Markham (client) / Correspondence A6510
Mason, Austin B., Jr. (client) / Blueline prints A4805
McClelland (client) / Correspondence A5814, A5911, A6007
McCreary, Mr. & Mrs. Lewis S. (client) / Construction drawings A5616
McFarland, Dr. & Mrs. Ross (client) / Invoices A7305
McGoldbrick (client) / Correspondence A6110
McGreal (client) / Blueprints A5706
Meyer, Mr. & Mrs. Alfred (client) / Construction drawings A5614
Miller, Theodore T. (client) / Construction drawings A365
Miller, Theodore T. (client) / Contracts A5505
Miller, Theodore T. (client) / Design development drawings A5417
Mitchell, Mrs. F.R. (client) / Articles B011
Mixter (client) / Blueprints A4714
Morgan (client) / Clippings A5926
Morse (client) / Project files A4617
Moulton (client) / Project files A5115
Munn, Mrs. James (client) / Invoices A7103
Munn (client) / Project files A4615
Nichols, W.H. (client) / Addenda A5917
Nichols (client) / Correspondence A6407
Norstad, Mrs. Lauris (client) / Notes A7201
Olmsted, George Jr. (client) / Construction drawings A376
Olmsted, Virginia (client) / Details A5517
Olmsted (client) / Construction drawings A4621
Olmsted (client) / Correspondence A6604
Osgood, Hamilton (client) / Cuts A7503
Osgood (client) / Design development drawings A5010
Otis, Thomas (client) / Invoices A6505
Paine, John A. (client) / Measured drawings A5018
Park, Mrs. Dorothy (client) / Correspondence A6108
Parker, Mr. & Mrs. Gordon (client) / Construction drawings A416
Parker, Mr. & Mrs. Gordon (client) / Project files A4914
Payne (contractor) / Blueprints A456
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Brochures A7206
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Clippings A4802
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Construction drawings A333, A343, A3515, A359, A364, A392, A404, A4814
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Contracts A6813
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Correspondence A5610, A5919, A6113, A6512, A6712
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Cuts A7208
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Diazo process prints A4711, A5210, A5314
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Measured drawings A7501
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Negatives A4414
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Outline specifications A3311
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Plot plans A5218
Peabody, Amelia (client) / Project files A4702, A4811
Peabody, Amelia (sculptress) / Correspondence A6702
Peakes (client) / Correspondence A6102